idosi.org 2018-12-12

# IDOSI Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

**Introduction**

Your privacy is important to IDOSI JOURNALS.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that IDOSI JOURNALS collects, and the ways in which IDOSI JOURNALS uses that personal information.

**Personal information collection**

IDOSI JOURNALS may collect and use personal information that is necessary for the processing and publication of manuscripts submitted to us. This information may include names, affiliation and contact details; including postal address, emails, phone numbers and fax numbers.

**Using personal information**

Any personal information received by IDOSI JOURNALS will only be used to: process and publish your manuscript. 

• administer this website;

• personalize the website for you;

• enable your access to and use of the website services;

• process your manuscript;

• publish your manuscript;

• send to you communication about your manuscript

• send to you statements and invoices;

• collect payments from you; and

• send you marketing communications.

Where IDOSI JOURNALS discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement. 

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, IDOSI JOURNALS may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**Securing your data**

IDOSI JOURNALS will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

**Cross-border data transfers**

Information that IDOSI JOURNALS collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which IDOSI JOURNALS operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**Updating this statement**

IDOSI JOURNALS may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.  

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.  

**Other websites**

This website contains links to other websites.  

IDOSI JOURNALS is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**Contact IDOSI JOURNALS**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or IDOSI JOURNALS' treatment of your personal information, please send an email to idosi.editor@gmail.com
